Hello friends, welcome to your own
YouTube channel Parivahan Help. Friends, today
I am going to upload the first video on this channel.
Our main objective of creating this channel is to provide
all the services related to transport,
such as
insurance, fitness permit, tax, pollution,
fancy number license and so on. All the
total information related to transport will be
given to you on this channel. So in today's video
we are going to talk about
how you can download the policy of Digital General Insurance Company
absolutely free. So
friends, let's start the video.
First of all, you have to go to Google's Chrome browser.
After going there, you have to
write Digital in the search bar. After that, you have to search and
click on it. First of all, you will
see the option Gold Rate General
Insurance. You have to click on it.
After clicking on it, you will
see the option on the left side in three dots.
You have to click on it.
After clicking on it, the option of Sign In will
appear. After typing on it, two options will
appear. Friends, enter Sign In with
mobile number and one option will appear below.
I want to tell you here
and Sign In with policy details. You have to click on this.
After clicking on this,
you have two options here.  You can download it from the option.
Now the first is registration and the second is
policy number. Friends, if you do
n't have a policy number, then you can download it by simply entering the vehicle's
registration number and the last digital number of the engine or chassis
number.
Friends, after entering the vehicle number and the last
five-digit number of the chassis, you will have to
scroll down a bit,
after that you will see the option to continue.
You have to type it on it.
After typing, you will have to wait for a few seconds.
After waiting, friends, here
you will see two options: Active Policy and
Expired Policy. You have to remember to
click on Active Policy.
After clicking on Active Policy,
you will see two options here. Friends, the first is
Download Policy. The second is Email Policy. If
you want to download the policy
instantly, then you have to click on Download Policy.
If you want to send the policy to email, then
you have to click on Email Policy.
Friends, if we want to
download the policy, then I will click on Download Policy.
You will have to
wait for it here, after that it will be downloaded.
Friends, I want to show you,
see, our policy copy has been created. It is the
original policy copy. You
can also save it.  So friends, how did
you like this video and if you
want to know any information related to transportation, then
subscribe to this channel and
press the bell icon so that you can get
all types of information related to transportation.
Thank you.